sonlet.com 2018-08-17

# Sonlet | Privacy

Welcome to Sonlet (“Sonlet”, “us”, “we”, or “our”). Sonlet provides services that aim to help direct sales consultants navigate the world, life, the universe, and everything (our “Services”). Directangular LLC (“Directangular”) operates Sonlet and https://sonlet.com (the "Site"). 

Our Privacy Policy explains how we use, share and protect information in relation to our Site. 

By using our Site and Services, you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you to post content, including photos, comments and other materials (collectively "Content"), to the Services and to share Content publicly. This means that other Users may search for, see, use, or share any of your Content that you make publicly available through the Services, consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use​. 

Our Privacy Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Services or Site (collectively "Users"). 

### Information Collection And Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, your e-mail address, and your phone number. ("Personal Information"). 

Log Data, like many site operators, collects information that your browser sends, whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). 

This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. 

In addition, we may use third-party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this Log Data. 

### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact with our Site updates and subscription changes. 

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to access some Services on our Site. 

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. But, remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Disclosure for Legal Reasons

We may share Personal Information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Sonlet, if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 

  * Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request. 
  * Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations. 
  * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 
  * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Sonlet, our Users or the public, as required or permitted by law. 

### Storage and Processing

Your information collected through the Services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Sonlet, Directangular, or its service providers maintain facilities. 

By registering for and using the Services you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or to any other country in which Sonlet, Directangular, or its service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We use commercially reasonable safeguards to help keep the information collected through the Site secure and take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. However, Sonlet cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to our Site or guarantee that information on the Services may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. 

Please do your part to help us! You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information. 

### Other Websites and Services

We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from our Site, including the information or content contained within them. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Site to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to those third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our Site, are subject to that third party's own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and do not have control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your Content. If you are using a third-party website or service and you allow them to access your Content you do so at your own risk. 

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date above and will remain in effect, except with respect to any future changes, which will go into effect immediately after being posted on this page. 

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We reserve the right to make changes, so you should periodically check this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services, after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy, will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will make an effort to notify you either through the email address you have provided us or by placing a prominent notice on our Site. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
